大学生活过得真快
College ran by real fast
因为我美式足球打得太多
'cause I played so much football.
他们还把我弄进一个什么东西
They even put me on a thing
叫做全美明星队
called the all-America team
那样你可以去见
where you get to meet
合众国的总统
the president of the United States.
肯尼迪总统接见了
President Kennedy met
全美大学足球队
with the collegiate all-American football team
在椭圆形办公室
at the Oval Office today .
那里最棒的一点
Now the really good thing
见合众国的总统的时候
about meeting the president of the United States
是食物
is the food.
他们让你呆在一个小房间里
They put you in this little room
里面有你爱吃或喝任何东西
with just about anything you'd want to eat or drink.
但是 因为第一：
But since, number one,
我不饿但是口渴
I wasn 't hungry but thirsty,
第二 这全是免费的
and number two, they was free,
我大概喝了15瓶汽水
I must have drank me about 15 Dr. Peppers.
入选全美明星队感觉如何？
How does it feel to be an all-American?
很荣幸 先生
It's an honor, sir.
入选全美明星队感觉如何？
How does it feel to be an all-American?
很好 先生
Very good, sir.
入选全美明星队感觉如何？
How does it feel to be an all-American ?
很好 先生
Very good, sir.
祝贺你 你感觉如何？
Congratulations. How do you feel?
我想撒尿
I got to pee.
我听着他好像说他想撒尿
I believe he said he had to pee.
不久之后,不知什么原因
Some time later, for noparticular reason,
有人枪杀了这位不错的年轻总统
somebody shot that nice young president
当时他坐着他的车
when he was riding in his car.
又过了几年
And a few years after that,
有人又枪杀了他的弟弟
somebody shot his little brother, too,
这次他是在一个酒店的厨房里
only he was in a hotel kitchen.
做兄弟可真不容易啊
Must be hard being brothers.
我不明白
I wouldn't know .
福雷斯甘
Forrest Gump.
你相信不相信？
Now can you believe it?
只不过玩了五年足球
After only five years of playing football,
我得到了大学学位
I got a college degree.
祝贺你 孩子
Congratulations, son.
妈妈骄傲极了
Mama was so proud.
福雷斯 我为你骄傲
Forrest, I'm so proud of you.
我替你拿着这个
I'll hold this for you.
祝贺你 孩子
Congratulations, son.
你有没有考虑过你的未来？
Have you given any thought to your future ?